{
    "subject": "resource/Goopy_Gyne_Bagha_Byne",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1969_films",
    "human_readable": "Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne is about 1969 films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9080954790115356,
            "question": "What is notable about Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8517352938652039,
            "question": "Is Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne a film series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8390174508094788,
            "question": "What year were Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne films released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.771929144859314,
            "question": "What is the story about in Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.713015079498291,
            "question": "Where were Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne films produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6713367700576782,
            "question": "Are Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne films popular in any specific regions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6049855947494507,
            "question": "Are there any sequels to Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.573379397392273,
            "question": "What genre is Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5619156360626221,
            "question": "Who are the directors of Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48066258430480957,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne is about 1969 films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4102_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the directors of Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4102_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4102_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any sequels to Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4102_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4102_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that confirm \"Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne\" is a 1969 film, thus supporting the statement that it is about 1969 films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}